digitaldoughnut.com 2019-05-02

# Privacy Policy - Digital Doughnut

## Privacy Policy

Digital Doughnut is part of Communitize Limited (“Communitize”) which also includes our services Demand Exchange and London Research. This privacy policy explains how we use any personal information we collect about you when you use this website.

Topics:

  * What information do we collect about you?
  * How will we use the information about you?
  * Marketing
  * Access to your information and correction
  * Cookies
  * Other websites
  * About our privacy policy
  * How to contact us

### What information do we collect about you?

We collect information about you when you register with us or place an order for events, products or services. We also collect information when you voluntarily complete customer surveys, provide feedback and participate in competitions. Website usage information is collected using cookies.

### How will we use the information about you?

We collect information about you to process your order, manage your account and, if you agree, to contact you about other products and services we think may be of interest to you. 

We use your information collected from the website to personalise your repeat visits to our website. If you agree, we shall pass on your personal information to other services within Communitize so that they may offer you their products and services.

Communitize will not share your information for marketing purposes with companies outside the company without your specific consent.

### Marketing

We would like to send you information about products and services of ours and other companies which may be of interest to you. If you have consented to receive marketing, you may opt out at a later date.

You have a right at any time to stop us from contacting you for marketing purposes or giving your information to our Demand Exchange and London Research services.

If you no longer wish to be contacted for marketing purposes, please [click here](mailto:unsubscribe@digitaldoughnut.com?subject=Please%20Unsubscribe).

### Access to your information and correction

You have the right to request a copy of the information that we hold about you. If you would like a copy of some or all of your personal information, please contact us at the following address: [datarequest@communitize.us](mailto:datarequest@communitize.us?subject=Data%20Request)

We want to make sure that your personal information is accurate and up to date. You may ask us to correct or remove information you think is inaccurate.

### Cookies

Cookies are text files placed on your computer to collect standard internet log information and visitor behaviour information. This information is used to track visitor use of the website and to compile statistical reports on website activity.

For further information visit www.aboutcookies.org or www.allaboutcookies.org.

You can set your browser not to accept cookies and the above websites tell you how to remove cookies from your browser. However in a few cases some of our website features may not function as a result.  Please see our Cookie Policy.

### Other websites

Our website contains links to other websites. This privacy policy only applies to this website so when you link to other websites you should read their own privacy policies.

### About our privacy policy

Our policy is in accordance with the Privacy and Electronic Communications (EC Directive) Regulations 2003 (“PECR”) and EU Regulation 2016/679 General Data Protection Regulation (“GDPR”). Personal data means any and all data that relates to an identifiable person who can be directly or indirectly identified from that data, as defined by GDPR.

We keep our privacy policy under regular review and we will place any updates on this web page. This privacy policy was last updated on 25th April 2018.

This privacy policy should be read in line with our terms and conditions and our cookie policy.

### How to contact us

Please contact us if you have any question s about our privacy policy or information we hold about you through our website, by [email](mailto:dpo@communitize.us) or by post at Communitize Limited, 35 Kingsland Road, London E2 8AA United Kingdom.

Communitize Limited’s Data Protection Officer is Mike Backs and is contactable on [DPO@communitize.us](mailto:DPO@communitize.us).
